

CONTACT

- +92 348 0214455
- ✓ MZohaibButt045@gmail.com
- Wah Cantt, Islamabad
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/zohaib -butt-0b1119269

EDUCATION

02/2020-01/2024 BACHELOR'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

COURSES

- Data Structures
- DBMS
- Object Oriented Programming
- Game Development
- HCI
- Artificial intelligence

SKILLS

- 3D Modeling and Animation
- UI & UX Design
- Game Design And Development
- Game Engine Proficiency(Unity)
- Programming Languages(C++,C#)
- Effective Communication
- Teamwork and Leadership
- Critical Thinking and Time Management

LANGUAGES

- English
- Urdu
- Punjabi
- Chinease(novice)

MUHAMMAD ZOHAIB

GAME DEVELOPER

PROFILE

As a game developer, I design and implement engaging gameplay mechanics, ensuring a seamless player experience. I collaborate with crossfunctional teams, including artists, designers, and marketers, to create immersive and marketable games. My role involves optimizing game performance, troubleshooting technical issues, and integrating user feedback to enhance gameplay. I have almost 2 years of experience in creating immersive game features and optimizing performance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PUGSDE SOLUTION

2023 - PRESENT

Jr Game Developer

- **Coins Hunter** (An engaging gameplay with coins collecting System Player have to find keys to pass on the next stage and).
- Bridge Race (User have to collect tiles and then move towards the bridge to make way to cross the bridge during this he have to face competitors and at the end anyone who first complete the way he will wins the race and stand first in that level).
- **Dragon Fire** (User get an Engaging Gameplay in which when hi click on the fire button the dragon will fire and if that fire hits the Enemy he will get damage and will die).

FREELANCING

2022-PRESENT

Developed and Sales

- Car Crashed (An engaging gameplay with a car crashed system user failed when he crashes the car, (Car Controller System)).
- Out of Sight (User have to play safe and complete the stage without facing enemies also he can kill them but it will be good that he didn't face them otherwise he also gets attacked and can be killed, (I use Navmesh and Built in Ai in Unity)).
- Shop Management (I have Developed a shop management system in which i can select the the item and it can dragabble and rotatable and the data is stored in Playerprefs).

UNIVERSITY PROJECTS

 Wreck-to-Riches(FYP): In this game Player will get an amazing and adventurous environment he have to wreck the crates that will be protected by Bots after killing them he gets alphabets and after completion he have to sort that alphabets by fixing puzzle.

REFERENCE

Engr. M. Naveed Butt

Projects Coordinator at NASTP

Phone: +92 333 5722090

Email: mnbuttpk@proton.me